check out this bright update in the
sunlife pH mobile app did you know that
you can withdraw funds from your V
policy for Urgent needs in a few tabs
here's how first log into your sunlife
pH mobile app then tap on the service
request button at the bottom and select
withdraw from my
vul select the vul policy you'd like to
withdraw from
type in the amount here's a tip withdraw
wisely type in the details of the bank
account you'd like the funds to be
transferred to to avoid delays make sure
to give accurate
information upload the required
documents these are important for us to
validate the details of your request
like your identity and bank
account this then review the details of
your request making sure that everything
is
correct once done click submit and
you're good to
go you can check the progress of your
request using the service request
tracker in the
app explore the sunlife pH app's other
features and manage your products
anytime anywhere the sunlife pH mobile
app your account in the p palm of your
hands now available for Android and iOS
from sunlife